



Yemane Gebreyohans

Date of birth: 05/04/1996 | **Nationality:** Ethiopian | **Gender:** Male | **Phone**

number: (+251) 0938435710 (Mobile) | **Email address:**

gebruyemane11@gmail.com

Address: Bole Subsity-AddisAbaba, 1000, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia (Work)

About me:

I have just over 4 year of experience as a Senior software developer with updated Technologies and I've already contributed over many projects
Prior to this role, I completed four-year in software development with Web
Development, where I honed my web development skills. Ideally, I would like to continue to specialize in web software development.

I have completed BSc. in Information Technology | Mekelle University offers a five-year Bachelor's degree program in Information Technology. I have studied data structures and algorithms, software engineering, mobile application development, database and database systems, web development and technologies, quick application development, networking, and mobile computing, among other things.

I attended Secondary and Preparatory School in TEMBEN, Tigray. From September 24, 2011 to July 7, 2015, I completed my high school and preparatory programs at WEKAMBA secondary and preparatory school in Temben Abiadi, Central Tigray.

I received my bachelor's degree in Information Technology Engineering from Mekelle University (IT).

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/03/2020 - 10/06/2021 Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS RCNDC SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PLC

- Car Rental Management System: I developed a car rental management system in Java Android and PHP for the web (by integrate both of them) and my role was full stack developer.
- Adimera E-commerce: I have used Nodejs(backend) and react (as a frontend) technologies to implement this ecommerce website. Here's how to get the ecommerce https://adimera.com and my role was full stack developer.
- AdeySpices E-commerce: I have used Nodejs(backend) and react (as a frontend) technologies to implement this ecommerce website. Here's how to get the ecommerce https://webshop.adeymeselesh.de/,https://admin-web-shop.adeymeselesh.de/#/ and my role was full stack developer
- Yehagere E-commerce: the system was developed using Nodejs(backend) and React(as a frontend), and I was the backend developer on this project. Here's how to get the ecommerce: Yehagere's website can be found at www.yehagere.com (on RCNDC Software PLC)
- Market Information Dissemination System: This system was developed using Laravel (backend) and AngularJS (frontend) frameworks, and I worked as a full-stack developer on this project.
- Suggestion Box Management System: this system was developed with Reactjs (as a frontend) and Nodejs (as a backend) for (Mekelle Institute of Technology) and my role was full stack developer.
- Automatic Id Card Generator: this system was a desktop app developed for MIT using Java and my role was full stack developer.

07/11/2018 - 03/08/2020 Mekelle, Ethiopia

SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS RENOSTAR IT SOLUTION PLC

• Court System Software: this software developed using Vuejs(as frontend) and Laravel(as backend).for Tigray Regional courts .

- Inventory and Finance Management System: I have developed this System using Qualified algorithms for AFFEOS(Abssinia foam Factory) campany in Mekelle as a fullstack developer using ASP.net as backend and React Redux as frontend and my role in the system was as full stack developer.
- **Human Resources and Registrar Management System**: this system is developed using nodejs(as backend) and React(as frontend) for Libanos and Betalogo colleges and my role in the system was as full stack developer.

02/08/2021 - CURRENT SchellingStrasse 22(Munich), Germany

SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS ADEY MESELESH SOFTWARE DEVELOPMET PLC

Haipetland Ecommerce Website: I have used Nodejs (as backend) and react(as frontend) to developed this ecommerce website. Here's how to get the ecommerce: https://web-shop.adeymeselesh.de/ 01/11/2022 - CURRENT Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS FARKA ICT SOLUTION PLC

- Senior Fullstack Software Developer using Nodejs, React, laravel and Vuejs technologies
- Minstery Of Education: I have used Laravel to developed this inspection system.my role was fullstack developer.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

10/05/2018 - 11/10/2018 Addis Ababa

CERTIFICATE OF APPRECIATION FOR PARTICIPATING IN TEACHING C, C++ AND PHP, JAVA AND BASIC COMPUTING FOR STUDENT OF MIT. Mekelle Institute Of technology(MIT)

Address Mekelle-Tigray, Addis Ababa

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **TIGRIGNA**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
AMHARIC	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user